phoneradar.com 2017-02-22

# Privacy Policy » PhoneRadar

[](https://i0.wp.com/phoneradar.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/Phoneradar-Privacy-Policy.png)PhoneRadar takes the privacy issues seriously, and the privacy of our visitors is very important to us. PhoneRadar is backed by Digital World Solutions, a company that owns a network of websites. We (PhoneRadar) do not use personal information of the users for any purpose, other than for the newsletters that we send, only if the user chooses to receive them.

Giving your information on our website while subscribing to newsletter, commenting on our pages is needed and if you choose to provide us your details, we do not use this information. It is though, obligatory to provide your email address while commenting on the website so as to verify that you are a human.

We use third party advertising networks for monetizing PhoneRadar.com, and most of these networks would use your visiting information (which still does not include your Name, Email address, Telephone Number even if you submit them for some purpose) so as to understand the traffic and provide advertisements based on the visitors interest, and to keep the advertisements relevant.

Following are the advertising networks that we use for the monetization and other purposes, and you may visit the Privacy policy pages of the websites to understand it better.

Google – http://www.google.com/privacy.html  
Sixapart – http://www.sixapart.com/privacy/  
Kontera – http://www.kontera.com/privacy.aspx  
Amazon – Amazon.com Privacy Notice  
Share A Sale – http://www.shareasale.com/w3c/policy.html  
Advertising – http://advertising.aol.com/privacy  
Tribal Fusion – http://www.tribalfusion.com/TribalFusion/privacy.html

**Where should we use your information**

We can and would use the information that you provide, to do the following (only if applicable):  
Send you regular newsletters, information about products on timely basis  
We can contact you any time for any account related contacting, if at all you have an account registered with us  
We can contact you if you won a prize in any contest held by us  
We may use the information to modify our advertisements and content but it won’t affect you in any way

**What is a Cookie, and how is it used**

While visiting a page on our website, the preferences set by you are stored in a file, called a Cookie. These cookies are used by our advertisers / third party networks to modify the advertisements and understand the user behavior on our website.

You will be asked to accept a cookie, and if you do that, each visit of yours on our website will be identified and the information will be collected for building up statistics and for general use for the advertisers.

There would be no sensitive personal information collected or used by either us, or our advertisers and third party services.

**Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

PhoneRadar is not affiliated with any third party service, and is wholly owned by backed by Digital World Solutions. None of the phone manufacturers or the Operating system providers are behind this.

Should you have any issues with our website or the privacy while visiting our website, contact us.

Share
